Jensen, Vernon Collection of International Longshoremen's Association's and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Materials 5487
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-113 (1973: June 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.73-113 (1973: June 29)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-114 (1973: July 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-115 (1973: July 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-116 (1973: July 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-117 (1973: July 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-118 (1973: July 9)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-119 (1973: July 10)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-120 (1973: July 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-121 (1973: July 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-122 (1973: July 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-123 (1973: July 16)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-124 (1973: July 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-125 (1973: July 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-126 (1973: July 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-127 (1973: July 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-128 (1973: July 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-129 (1973: July 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-130 (1973: July 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-131 (1973: July 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-132 (1973: July 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-133 (1973: July 30)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.73-134 (1973: July 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-135 (1973: Aug. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-136 (1973: Aug. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-137 (1973: Aug. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-138 (1973: Aug. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-139 (1973: Aug. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-140 (1973: Aug. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-141 (1973: Aug. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-142 (1973: Aug. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-143 (1973: Aug. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-144 (1973: Aug. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-145 (1973: Aug. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-146 (1973: Aug. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-147 (1973: Aug. 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-148 (1973: Aug. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-149 (1973: Aug. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-150 (1973: Aug. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-151 (1973: Aug. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-152 (1973: Aug. 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-153 (1973: Aug. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-154 (1973: Aug. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-155 (1973: Aug. 29)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-156 (1973: Aug. 30)
  - Item 23: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.73-157 (1973: Aug. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-158 (1973: Sep. 4)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-159 (1973: Sep. 5)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-160 (1973: Sep. 6)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-161 (1973: Sep. 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-162 (1973: Sep. 10)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-163 (1973: Sep. 11)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-164 (1973: Sep. 12)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-165 (1973: Sep. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-166 (1973: Sep. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-167 (1973: Sep. 17)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-168 (1973: Sep. 18)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-169 (1973: Sep. 19)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-170 (1973: Sep. 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-171 (1973: Sep. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-172 (1973: Sep. 24)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-173 (1973: Sep. 25)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-174 (1973: Sep. 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-175 (1973: Sep. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.73-176 (1973: Sep. 28)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-177 (1973: Oct. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-178 (1973: Oct. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-179 (1973: Oct. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-180 (1973: Oct. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-181 (1973: Oct. 5)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-182 (1973: Oct. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-183 (1973: Oct. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-184 (1973: Oct. 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-185 (1973: Oct. 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-186 (1973: Oct. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-187 (1973: Oct. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-188 (1973: Oct. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-189 (1973: Oct. 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-190 (1973: Oct. 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-191 (1973: Oct. 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-192 (1973: Oct. 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-193 (1973: Oct. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-194 (1973: Oct. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-195 (1973: Oct. 29)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-196 (1973: Oct. 30)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.73-197 (1973: Oct. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-198 (1973: Nov. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-199 (1973: Nov. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-200 (1973: Nov. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-201 (1973: Nov. 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-202 (1973: Nov. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-203 (1973: Nov. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-204 (1973: Nov. 12)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-205 (1973: Nov. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-206 (1973: Nov. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-207 (1973: Nov. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-208 (1973: Nov. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-209 (1973: Nov. 19)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-210 (1973: Nov. 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-211 (1973: Nov. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-212 (1973: Nov. 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-213 (1973: Nov. 26)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-214 (1973: Nov. 27)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-215 (1973: Nov. 28)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-216 (1973: Nov. 29)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.73-217 (1973: Nov. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-218 (1973: Dec. 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-219 (1973: Dec. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-220 (1973: Dec. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-221 (1973: Dec. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-222 (1973: Dec. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-223 (1973: Dec. 10)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-224 (1973: Dec. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-225 (1973: Dec. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-226 (1973: Dec. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-227 (1973: Dec. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-228 (1973: Dec. 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-229 (1973: Dec. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-230 (1973: Dec. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-231 (1973: Dec. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-232 (1973: Dec. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-233 (1973: Dec. 26)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-234 (1973: Dec. 27)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.73-235 (1973: Dec. 28)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-2 (1974: Jan. 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-3 (1974: Jan. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-4 (1974: Jan. 7)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-5 (1974: Jan. 8)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-6 (1974: Jan. 9)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-7 (1974: Jan. 10)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-8 (1974: Jan. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-9 (1974: Jan. 14)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-10 (1974: Jan. 15)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-11 (1974: Jan. 16)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-12 (1974: Jan. 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-13 (1974: Jan. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-14 (1974: Jan. 21)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-15 (1974: Jan. 22)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-16 (1974: Jan. 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-17 (1974: Jan. 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-18 (1974: Jan. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-19 (1974: Jan. 28)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-20 (1974: Jan. 29)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-21 (1974: Jan. 30)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.74-22 (1974: Jan. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-23 (1974: Feb. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-24 (1974: Feb 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-25 (1974: Feb 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-26 (1974: Feb 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-27 (1974: Feb 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-28 (1974: Feb 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-29 (1974: Feb 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-30 (1974: Feb 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-31 (1974: Feb 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-32 (1974: Feb 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-33 (1974: Feb 19)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-34 (1974: Feb 20)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-35 (1974: Feb 21)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-36 (1974: Feb 22)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-37 (1974: Feb 25)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-38 (1974: Feb 26)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-39 (1974: Feb 27)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.74-40 (1974: Feb 28)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-41 (1974: Mar. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-42 (1974: Mar. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-43 (1974: Mar. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-44 (1974: Mar. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-45 (1974: Mar. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-46 (1974: Mar. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-47 (1974: Mar. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-48 (1974: Mar. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-49 (1974: Mar. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-50 (1974: Mar. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-51 (1974: Mar. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-52 (1974: Mar. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-53 (1974: Mar. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-54 (1974: Mar. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-55 (1974: Mar. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-56 (1974: Mar. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-57 (1974: Mar. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-58 (1974: Mar. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-59 (1974: Mar. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-60 (1974: Mar. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.74-61 (1974: Mar. 29)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-62 (1974: Apr. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-63 (1974: Apr. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-64 (1974: Apr. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-65 (1974: Apr. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-66 (1974: Apr. 5)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-67 (1974: Apr. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-68 (1974: Apr. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-69 (1974: Apr. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-70 (1974: Apr. 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-71 (1974: Apr. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-72 (1974: Apr. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-73 (1974: Apr. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-74 (1974: Apr. 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-75 (1974: Apr. 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-76 (1974: Apr. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-77 (1974: Apr. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-78 (1974: Apr. 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-79 (1974: Apr. 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-80 (1974: Apr. 26)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-81 (1974: Apr. 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.74-82 (1974: Apr. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-83 (1974: May 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-84 (1974: May 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-85 (1974: May 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-86 (1974: May 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-87 (1974: May 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-88 (1974: May 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-89 (1974: May 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-90 (1974: May 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-91 (1974: May 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-92 (1974: May 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-93 (1974: May 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-94 (1974: May 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-95 (1974: May 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-96 (1974: May 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-97 (1974: May 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-98 (1974: May 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-99 (1974: May 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-100 (1974: May 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-101 (1974: May 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-102 (1974: May 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-103 (1974: May 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.74-104 (1974: May 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-105 (1974: June 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-106 (1974: June 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-107 (1974: June 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-108 (1974: June 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-109 (1974: June 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-110 (1974: June 10)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-111 (1974: June 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-112 (1974: June 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-113 (1974: June 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-114 (1974: June 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-115 (1974: June 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-116 (1974: June 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-117 (1974: June 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-118 (1974: June 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-119 (1974: June 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-120 (1974: June 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-121 (1974: June 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-122 (1974: June 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-123 (1974: June 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.74-124 (1974: June 28)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-125 (1974: July 1)